<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string name="hello">Hello World! Hello Horoscopes!</string>
	<string name="app_name">Horoscopes</string>
	<string name="rabbit">Rabbit</string>
	<string name="snake">Snake</string>
	<string name="tiger">Tiger</string>
	<string name="horse">Horse</string>
	<string name="sheep">Sheep</string>
	<string name="sheep_desc">Years:\nSheep Years are eighth in the cycle
		following the Horse Years, and recur every twelfth
		year.\n\nCharacteristics:\nSmart, Artistic, Kind, Happy, Reserved,
		Insecure, Dependent.\n\nSheep simply want a bit of peace. They enjoy
		carrying on with life in their own quiet, individual way, content to
		be in the middle of it all rather than to be leading it. Sheep are
		quiet and calm people. They enjoy cultural things and focus much of
		their energy on artistic hobbies. Sheep are easy going and relaxed,
		happy to be going with the flow.
	</string>
	<string name="rabbit_desc">Years:\nRabbit Years are fourth in the cycle,
		following Tiger Years, and recur every twelfth
		year.\n\nCharacteristics:\nKeen, Wise, Fragile, Tranquil, Serene,
		Considerate, Fashionable, Sneaky, Obsessive.\n\nRabbits are private
		individuals, a bit introverted and withdrawn. People born into this
		sign would rather work behind-the-scenes instead of being the center
		of attention in any situation. Do not misunderstand … the Rabbit is
		not a recluse. In fact, he is a reasonably friendly individual who
		enjoys the company of a group of good friends whether at a business
		dinner or a holiday party. Rabbits just like to be a part of the gang
		as opposed to the leader of it.
	</string>
	<string name="snake_desc">Years:\nSnake Years are sixth in the cycle,
		following the Dragon Years, and recur every twelfth
		year.\n\nCharacteristics:\nAcute, Aware, Cunning, Proud, Vain,
		Vicious.\n\nAncient Chinese wisdom says a Snake in the house is a good
		omen because it means your family will not starve. This could be taken
		metaphorically to mean that a Snake could never have a problem with
		his family starving because he is such a great mediator, making him
		good at business. Or it could mean that a Snake would be willing to
		sacrifice his possessions, something the Snake has a lot of, in order
		to pay for his family’s food. Any way it is interpreted is
		representative of the Snake’s character and is a measure of the value
		he puts on his material wealth. The Snake is keen and cunning, quite
		intelligent and wise.
	</string>
	<string name="horse_desc">Years:\nHorse Years are seventh in the cycle,
		following the Snake Years, and recur every twelfth
		year.\n\nCharacteristics:\nSelf-reliant, Joyful, Outgoing,
		Sophisticated, Greedy, Resilient, Arrogant.\n\nExciting and
		extroverted, vivid and animated, the Horse is the life of any party he
		attends. He is bursting with energy, always looking for the next place
		to kick up his heels and hang loose. He entertains friends and
		strangers alike with his humor and appeal.
	</string>
	<string name="tiger_desc">Years:\nTiger Years are third in the cycle and
		recur every twelfth year.\n\nCharacteristics:\nCourage, Vehemence,
		Self-Reliance, Friendliness, Hopefulness, Resilience, Vanity,
		Disregard.\n\nThe Tiger is said to be lucky vivid, lively and
		engaging. Another attribute of the Tiger is his incredible bravery,
		evidenced in his willingness to engage in battle or his undying
		courage. Maybe he’s so brave because he is so lucky. But the Chinese
		say a Tiger having a Tiger in the house is the very best protection
		against the evils of fire, burglary.
	</string>
	<string-array name="horoscope_array">
		<item>Horse</item>
		<item>Tiger</item>
		<item>Rabbit</item>
		<item>Sheep</item>
		<item>Snake</item>
	</string-array>
	<string-array name="horse_friend">
		<item>Salma</item>
		<item>Sara</item>
		<item>Fatema</item>
	</string-array>
	<string-array name="sheep_friend">
		<item>Aya</item>
		<item>Jamica</item>
		<item>Heba</item>
	</string-array>
	<string-array name="snake_friend">
		<item>Marwa</item>
		<item>Ahmed</item>
		<item>Huda</item>
		<item>Noha</item>
	</string-array>
	<string-array name="dragon_friend"/>
	<string-array name="rabbit_friend"/>
	<string name="horoscope_prompt">Choose a Horoscope</string>
</resources>
